Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Yami had just arrived at the Golden Dawn Headquarters for a meeting with Vaanjin, Swin.
I thought old Goldie Guts called me here to apologize.
What's a big idea making me wait around all day? How much longer is this gonna take?
I'm sure that he'll be here as soon as possible.
You playing me for a fool, Golden Dawn?
Yami continued to wait, trusting the man who'd fought alongside him on behalf of their nation,
and with whom he'd become a Magic Knight captain.
But in the meantime, Vaanjinz was revealing his alternate identity during a confrontation with the Wizard King.
With two separate souls inhabiting his body at once, he was not only Captain William Vaanjinz of the Golden Dawn,
but also Ligt, the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
William, my only human friend, I know this was hard for you. I'm grateful.
Greetings to you, Wizard King Julius Novakrono. I am the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun, known as Ligt.
I've dreaded this day, yet here we are.
Ligt challenged Julius to a battle, hoping to steal the final two magic stones he needed to enact his revenge against humankind.
But Julius used time magic to predict and block his attacks.
It's over.
His predictions are improving.
I can already see your future, and I can assure you it ends in defeat.
It's over.
Well...
That will be fun and episode 2.
Yes!
My identity has been blessed, but I really don't set me up.
Love to take notes.
The past chapter, final line is judgment upon you.
You will have never proceed to Shimane music with a record than determines who is gunfire,
ettre more nor do rice.
How is it?
It's over.
The Magic apron, you aim me out.
Once you be blessed, harder than you know.
This one is the planet
I were capable of
So everyone is perfect
Didn't say good
I fully
I can't aces
My hope
rence
Hey, look! The castle tower!
What are all those flashes?
Something's going on up there!
Over here!
Look, sir!
That tower, it's Julius. He must be fighting someone.
A light magic user strong enough to be holding his own against the Wizard King.
Who else could it be but the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Licked.
Except, the Royal Knights are supposed to be out on a mission to eliminate him right now.
How did he get to the castle? Is the Midnight Sun to blame for the communication breakdown between me and Julius?
There's so much we don't know.
What's happening out there?
Is Sir Julius fighting with somebody?
What can we do to stop this?
Please remain calm.
Our mettle may be tested in times like this.
But we'll never be able to defend Clover Kingdom if we let panic overtake us.
That's right. Just stay calm.
Now, more than ever, my duty is to keep a cool head.
If any of us got involved, the difference in skill would only hold Julius back.
I don't expect he'll be defeated.
If it came down to it, the only Knight's fit to join the fray would be Captain Calibur.
I'll send an alert to all the Magic Knight headquarters.
What the heck?
Hey, Char.
A transmission spell?
A call from the Royal Capital, sir.
This is an urgent message to all Captains.
The Wizard King is at Clover Castle fighting someone who appears to be the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
As was the case with the previous assault on the capital.
It's possible that they're plotting multiple attacks.
Knights, please follow your Captain's orders on where to stand guard.
And Captains, finish organizing your guard squads and assemble in the Royal Capital.
I don't understand this.
Yeah, I thought Captain Mara Leona was infiltrating their hideout.
Their leader is attacking the Royal Capital?
This is the perfect chance to avenge my brother.
But...
What's with all these pitiful faces?
You dare to call yourselves members of the Crimson Lion King?
Sir!
Remember what my brother said to you.
It's always best to stay calm.
Even though my sister isn't here, we will follow the instructions from the capital and attack the enemy on our own.
He's got a point.
This is no time for us to falter.
Yeah, we're the Crimson Lion Kings!
It says we're to follow orders, but the Captain is nowhere to be found.
I sure hope Captain Vongens gets back soon.
Don't tell me.
I hope I'm wrong about this.
Your attacks are growing quite pedestrian.
Even without looking into the future, I don't think I'll have very much trouble avoiding them.
I don't think I'll have very much trouble in the future, but I don't think I'll have very much trouble in the future.
I don't think I'll have very much trouble in the future.
He can keep up with me at this speed?
Just how far into the future is this human able to see?
Is this yours?
He sped up my spell and threw it back.
Wow, close call.
Despite my ability to see what you're going to do next, you're too quick on your feet for me to catch up with you.
You know, you'd be awfully helpful to me if you'd surrender right about now.
I wouldn't want to cause any damage to Vongens' body.
So he won't kill me.
He's trying to capture me instead.
He's holding back.
Against me and my four-leaf grimoire?
All right.
Then what must his be like?
And where could it be?
I assume you must be getting curious about my grimoire.
You're welcome to examine it for yourself.
It's right up there.
It doesn't even have a cover.
What kind of grimoire has a bizarre shape like that?
I'm a time magic user with a coverless grimoire.
I never knew whether that was good or bad, but I could tell that it meant I was something special.
I thought hard about it.
And I realized that this grimoire and I have a lot in common.
Neither of us fits into a particular category.
So who am I really?
What am I meant to achieve?
I asked myself these questions for years.
And the more I learned, the more I wondered.
After I'd made it this far, it was finally clear.
The path I'd walked all this way, that is me.
I am the Wizard King.
Yes, I understand now.
What we're planning to do once we have the magic stones
will be an attempt to violate the natural laws of this world.
So this man, this human,
he must have been placed here by fate itself in order to thwart our ambitions.
He is the final bastion of reason.
And as the Wizard King,
I'll protect the people of Clover.
Come what may.
I knew it.
That's all the more reason
why I must end his life.
Protect them?
Go ahead and try!
Sealing magic,
release!
He's expanded his power.
Hey, what's that?
Look up in the sky!
Oh dear, what's going to happen now?
It's absolutely gargantuan.
Humans took away everything.
All of our happiness.
Our friends and loved ones.
Our peaceful days.
Just like that.
It may be an affront to reason,
but you'll atone for your sins.
Now die!
He's been holding on to enough power
to cover the entire kingdom.
Is he going to release all of that magic
and wipe out the whole populace?
I may not be able to kill you,
but I can easily exterminate everybody else.
Whoa, is that magic?
Swords of light, thousands of them!
Look, Mama!
This knife's full of swords!
So bright!
Those blades could kill us all!
Is this how the world ends?
It's unbelievable.
What's that bright light?
It's way over there.
I have a bad feeling.
It's alright.
Even if it turns out to be something dangerous,
we'll always have the brave magic knights
to guard the Clover Kingdom.
The big hunk of light magic.
Damn it.
What the hell is this, Julius?
I gotta hurry!
His spell's already covering everything in sight
at this rate.
Now.
Here is your punishment, humans!
Light magic!
Arrows of judgment!
I did have my doubts.
Honestly,
why do the regular folk have such pathetic magic
compared to people like us?
I couldn't agree more.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not sure why commoners exist in the first place.
We shouldn't have to share the same country with them.
I'll drink to that.
But is that really true?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
They had strong magic power,
and yet the only thing they ever used it for
was to selflessly line their own pockets.
Why did these useless mages exist?
I see.
You're that magic knight, aren't you?
Yes.
The one with the strange grimoire?
Well, no matter.
Anyway,
I was about to tell you
there's a merchant
who wants me to give his business a leg up.
Really?
No.
We'll talk.
I can't wait to hear.
I kept fighting in my magic knight squad,
hoping I'd eventually discover my calling.
Then, one day...
Go, go, please.
Let him go!
Give me all your yule
or I'll bash your face in.
Hold it!
You villains are always disturbing the peace,
and I'm fed up with it.
I met Zara,
the very first commoner
to be selected as a member of the Magic Knights.
We'll fight if you want,
but so you know,
my magic's about a hundred times tougher
than anything you can throw at me.
A magic knight, huh?
Am I supposed to be scared of you
or something, pal?
That's a bad move.
Had enough?
Now, go find somewhere safe.
Thank you.
We're so glad you showed up.
Hey, you!
Do me a favor!
Come down for a sec!
His power itself was weak,
but his strategic fighting style
made full use of trap magic.
It was clear he had worked hard to master it.
What kind of crazy spell is that?
It's almost like you're turning back time or something.
It looks that way,
but that's not exactly the case.
Time magic, huh?
That is impressive.
Seems like it would be a surefire way
to prevent casualties.
You're Zara, aren't you?
It appears that you're injured as well.
Sit down and rest so I can take a look.
Nah, I'll be all right.
When you're a magic knight,
you're supposed to put the lives
of the civilians first.
You agree?
Don't you, Julius?
Okay, this guy seems fine.
Unlike all the knights
who were selfishly seeking glory,
he was truly prioritizing
the lives of the people he saved.
I still didn't know
what a magic knight
was really supposed to be,
but even I saw
that he was the genuine article.
Later on,
I learned that Zara had died.
Zara had carried out his duty
as a magic knight,
and I wanted to follow
in his footsteps.
I was finally sure
of my purpose in life,
to become the kind of knight
he was.
They're saying he was murdered
by one of his own squad members.
Really?
Well, we can't have a nasty rumor
like that going around.
Word is,
he was prying into things
he shouldn't.
What's one dead commoner, anyway?
No one's going to miss him.
How could this possibly be right?
And it wasn't just
among the magic knights, either.
It was the way
the country had always been.
The class system
made the nobles prideful,
and the commoners hopeless.
There had to be more.
On both sides of the coin,
magic potential,
human potential,
is infinite.
But to be heard,
I needed power,
standing,
and trust.
I devoted my efforts
to producing results,
and became the wizard king.
Surely magic and people
should be more free.
It hasn't happened overnight,
but I can see now
that little by little,
this kingdom and its people
are finally beginning to change.
After all,
the ones I came to trust
and respect
combined their strength,
as well as the strength
of those who they trusted.
As the wizard king,
I can't let it end here.
I refuse to.
Time reversal magic.
Chrono Anastasis.
What's happening now?
Your time magic was enough
to save them.
Impressive.
Though it would appear
you've used all the time
and power you had saved up.
You would have seen
this attack of mine coming.
But unfortunately,
you weren't able to call off
that final time magic spell
in order to get out of the way.
Because you're...
the wizard king.
The wizard king.
And being the wizard king
is your one
and only weakness.
What happened here?
Tell me, Fungence.
切な何かに不可笑になって
臆病な自分を隠していた
I don't need no money
I don't need no魔力は要らない
自力で挑んだミラクル
起きること願い
微力ながら1ミリずつ
ビリビリ切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
My disability is my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って
嫌いになって
負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に
立ち向かう勇気へと
導いてく our treasure
無限らないのは
最高にで there's love
かざしたちがい
ひっかりが
生きる treasure
Please remain calm.
That's right. Just stay calm.
Now, more than ever, my duty is to keep a cool head.
I don't expect he'll be defeated.
If it came down to it, the only knight's fit to join the fray would be Captain Calibur.
I'll send an alert to all the Magic Knight headquarters.
You've reached my Magic is Never Giving Up bar and grill. What's your order?
I'm sorry. I must have called the wrong place.
Okay. This time I'll call the Magic Knight.
Thank you for calling the Melty Mana Hot Spring Resort. Are you making a reservation?
No, thanks. I'm fine.
One more try.
And who might this be?
Uh, hello there, ma'am. Is this a Magic Knight headquarters?
I told you people, I don't want any!
Damn! I can't get through. What the hell am I doing wrong here?
It's okay. Just stay calm.
Right.
What's gotten into you, Vangeans?
You just betrayed Julius' trust in my friendship.
And for that, you deserve to die.
Black Clover, page 94.
New future.
Dark magic, dark cloaked, dimension slash!